Guide to the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Francois Mergen, 1962-1977; Accession 1982-A-018
  - Subject/Correspondence files, 1962-1977, Series I
    - International Agricultural Development Service, 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 212)
    - International Office, 1964-1968 (Box 16, Folder 213)
    - "International Symposium on Statistical Ecology", 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 214-214a)
    - International Union of Forestry Research Organizations, 1967-1971 (Box 17, Folder 215-216)
    - Inventory Report on Nelson Ranch - Prepared for Jaime Raigosa, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 216a)
    - Inventory Report on Nelson Ranch for Z. W. White, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 216b)
    - Invitations etc., 1969-1974 (Box 17, Folder 217)
    - "Issues in the Environmental Crisis" - Parts III - VI, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 218-221)
    - J Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 17, Folder 222)
    - K Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 17, Folder 223)
    - L Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 17, Folder 225)
    - Law School, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 226)
    - Legislative Apprenticeship, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 227)
    - Library - Forestry School, 1965-1970 (Box 18, Folder 228)
    - Library - Sterling Memorial, 1966-1970 (Box 18, Folder 229)
    - Logging and Utilization at Yale School of Forestry, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 230)
    - M Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 18, Folder 232-233)
    - Mailing List: Change to Mergen from Garrett, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 234)
    - Mc Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 18, Folder 235)
    - McIntyre - Stennis Act, 1965-1969 (Box 18, Folder 237)
    - Medical School, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 238)
    - Meetings Attended, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 239)
    - Michigan, University of: Correspondence, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 240)
    - MICOVA - New England Council, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 241)
    - Milford Reunion, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 242)
    - Military Draft: Related Matters, 1967-1970 (Box 19, Folder 243)
    - Moratorium for Protest of War, 1969 October 15 (Box 19, Folder 244)
    - N Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 19, Folder 249)
    - National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council, 1965-1970 (Box 19, Folder 250)
    - National Research Council - Committee on Resources and Man, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 251)
    - National Science Foundation - Correspondence etc., 1965-1970 (Box 20, Folder 252)
    - National Science Foundation - Visiting Scientist Program, 1967-1970 (Box 20, Folder 253)
    - Natural Science Advisory Committee for Summer 1976, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 254)
    - New England Consortium on Environmental Protection, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 255)
    - New England Council, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 256)
    - New England Natural Resources Center - Symposium on New England Forest Land Use Policy, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 257)
    - News Bureau - Correspondence etc., 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 258)
    - News Releases and Clippings, 1964-1968 (Box 20, Folder 259-260)
    - News Releases (1 of 2), 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 261)
    - News Releases (2 of 2), 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 262)
    - News Releases, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 263)
    - Northeastern Forest Experiment Station, 1966-1968 (Box 21, Folder 264)
    - Northeas tern Forest Tree Improvement Conference, 1965-1969 (Box 21, Folder 265)
    - Northeastern Forestry Research Advisory Committee, 1966-1974 (Box 21, Folder 266-269)
    - Northeastern Region of Planned Parenthood - World Population - dinner, 1970 April (Box 21, Folder 270)
    - O Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 22, Folder 271)
    - Objectives of Forestry School, Faculty Comments on, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 274)
    - Objectives and Functions of Yale Forestry School, Memo to President Brewster, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 275)
    - Objectives of the Forestry School, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 276)
    - Old Blue Yale Tract "Cruise Sheet'', 1966 (Box 22, Folder 276a)
    - Organization for Tropical Studies, 1968-1971 (Box 22, Folder 277)
    - P Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 22, Folder 278)
    - Peace Corps, 1963-1969 (Box 22, Folder 279)
    - Personnel Office, 1965-1970 (Box 23, Folder 280)
    - Physical Plant and Housekeeping Service, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 281)
    - President's Office - Kingman Brewster, 1965-1970 (Box 23, Folder 282-283)
    - Proposal to the.Rrovost for Establishment of Master of Forest Science Degree, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 284)
    - Provost: Davld B.H. Martin, 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 285)
    - Provost's Office: General Information and Procedures, 1964-1969 (Box 23, Folder 286)
    - Publicity: New Dean and New Program, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 287)
    - Purchases, Bureau of, 1966-1969 (Box 23, Folder 288)
    - R Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 23, Folder 289)
    - Radiation Safety Committee, 1967-1971 (Box 23, Folder 290)
    - Reception of the Dean, 1966-1972 (Box 24, Folder 291-297)
    - Recruiting of Students, 1965-1969 (Box 24, Folder 298)
    - S Correspondence, 1966-1972 (Box 24, Folder 300-301)
    - Scholarship and Fellowship Announcements of Yale School of Forestry, 1963-1968 (Box 24, Folder 302)
    - School Progress Reaches Each District (SPRED) Instruction, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 302a)
    - Science of Creative Intelligence, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 303)
    - Scientists for a Quality Environment, Committee of, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 304)
    - Secretary's Office: Sam Chauncey, 1966-1969 (Box 24, Folder 305)
    - Selective Service and Veterans' Affairs, 1966-1969 (Box 25, Folder 306)
    - Seminar Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 307)
    - Service Bureau, 1964-1966 (Box 25, Folder 308)
    - Southern Field Trip: Silviculture - Management, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 308a)
    - Southern Forest Institute, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 309)
    - Spring Camp - Crosset, Arkansas [See: Garrett Series I, Folder 425], 1962-1966
    - Steady State Activities - NY Times, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 310)
    - Strike of Student Protest, Correspondence re:, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 311)
    - Student Committees, Yale School of Forestry, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 312)
    - Student Employment, Summer, 1965-1968 (Box 25, Folder 313)
    - Student Enrollment, 1966-1967 (Box 25, Folder 314)
    - Summer Activities Office and Registration, 1965-1970 (Box 25, Folder 315)
    - Systems Ecology - Positions, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 316)
    - T Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 26, Folder 317)
    - Teaching and Research Funds: Allocations, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 318)
    - Technical Association of the Pulp and Paper Industry (TAPPI)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 26, Folder 319)
      - Forest Biology Committee, 1968-1975 (Box 26, Folder 320-321)
      - Forest Biology Conference, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 322)
    - Timber Supply Act: H.R. 12025, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 323)
    - Travels of the Dean, 1967-1971 (Box 26, Folder 324-325)
    - Treasurer's Office - Spencer Miller - Correspondence, 1958-1968 (Box 26, Folder 326)
    - Treasurer's Office - Data Systems Policies, Forms, etc., 1964-1966 (Box 26, Folder 327)
    - Tropical Woods
      - General Correspondence, 1965-1973 (Box 26, Folder 328)
      - Memoranda of Agreement, 1964-1965 (Box 26, Folder 329)
      - University Microfilms, Catalogue of Back Issues, 1961-1966 (Box 26, Folder 330)
    - Tuition at Other Forestry Schools, 1962-1963 (Box 26, Folder 331)
    - Tuition Postponement Option, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 332)
    - U Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 27, Folder 333)
    - Udall, Stewart K. "Overview", 1969 (Box 27, Folder 334)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture
      - 1965-1971 (Box 27, Folder 335)
      - Plant Import Permit - Plant Quarantine Division - USDA, 1964-1967 (Box 27, Folder 336)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education & Welfare, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 337)
    - U.S. Department of the Interior, 1966-1968 (Box 27, Folder 338)
    - U.S. Plywood - Champion Lectures, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 339-340)
    - U.S. Plywood - Champion Paper Inc., 1964-1968 (Box 27, Folder 341)
    - University Council, 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 342-344)
    - University Council, 1970-1972 (Box 28, Folder 345-347)
    - University Council: Committee on the School of Forestry, 1970-1973 (Box 28, Folder 348-349)
    - University Dining Halls and Housekeeping Services, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 350)
    - University Research Institute of Connecticut, Inc., 1967 (Box 28, Folder 351)
    - Urban and Environmental Science, Ph.D. Program in - Ad Hoc Committee, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 352)
    - V Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 28, Folder 354)
    - Vehicles, 1967-1970 (Box 28, Folder 356)
    - Visiting Lecturer Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 357)
    - Visiting Lecturers, 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 358)
    - W Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 29, Folder 359-360)
    - WESTVACO - General, 1965-1971 (Box 29, Folder 361)
    - Western Forestry & Conservation Conference, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 362)
    - Weyerhaeuser, George, 1966-1976 (Box 29, Folder 363)
    - Wildlife Society, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 364)
    - Wood Science and Technology, Society of, 1965-1977 (Box 29, Folder 367)
    - World Consulation on Forest Tree Breeding, 2nd - Northeastern Tour, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 368)
    - World Consultation on Forestry Education and Training, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 369)
    - World Consultation of Forestry School Executives, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 370)
    - World Forestry Conference, Sixth, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 371)
    - World Forestry Conference, Seventh, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 372)
    - World Hunger, Seminar on: Rev. William S. Coffin, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 373)
    - World Peace Day: Congregation Mishkan Israel, Hamden, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 374)
    - Y Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 29, Folder 375)
    - Yale College: correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 30, Folder 376)
    - Yale Election Strategy Fund, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 377)
    - Yale Forestry School News, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 378-381)
    - Yale - Inter-office Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 30, Folder 382-383)
    - Yale Medal, 1966-1970 (Box 30, Folder 384)
    - Yale National Alumni Meeting
      - Chicago, Illinois, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 385)
      - Seattle, Washington, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 386)
    - Yale Natural Preserve
      - 1967 (Box 31, Folder 387)
      - Bethany Bog Acquisition, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 388)
      - Committee Meetings, 1955-1966 (Box 31, Folder 389)
      - Correspondence etc., 1953-1967 (Box 31, Folder 390-391)
      - Flora and Fauna, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 393)
      - Linsley Pond Acquisition, 1964-1972 (Box 31, Folder 394)
      - Maps and Keys, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 395)
      - Reports, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 396)
    - Z Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 31, Folder 397)
    - Restricted
      Restricted 75 years from date of file.
      - Admissions Committee, 1966-1975 (Box 32, Folder 399-407)
      - Degrees in Biological Sciences, Committee for, 1965-1969 (Box 33, Folder 410)
      - Doctoral Admission and Financial Aid, 1972-1974 (Box 33, Folder 412-413)
      - Enrollment, 1964-1968 (Box 33, Folder 414)
      - Financial Aid, 1971-1974 (Box 33, Folder 415-418)
      - International Office, 1964-1968 (Box 33, Folder 422)
      - International Union of Forest Research Organizations - Awards Committee, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 423)
      - Resumes Received, 1968-1972 (Box 34, Folder 424-425)
      - Salary Sheets, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 426)
  - Faculty Positions
    - Biology, Department of: Appointment of Margaret Bryan Davis, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Biomathematics - Candidates' Files, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Biometeorology - Heinz Helmut Lettan, 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Biometeorolgy, Lectureship in, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Ecology - Uninterested Candidates, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Forest Ecology, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Forest Entomology, 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 8-10)
    - Forest Genetics, 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Forest Pathology - Candidates' Files, 1960-1966 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Forest Pathology - J.P. van Buijtenen, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Forest Pathology "Dead File", 1966 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Forest Pathology Position Solicitations, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Forestry Management and Forest Hydrology, 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Forestry Management Position, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - General Wildlife - Applicants, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Hydrology, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Industrial Forestry - Announcements and General File, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Industrial Forestry - Candidates' Files, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 21-23)
    - Land Use, Visiting Lecturers in, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Land Use Planning, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Logging, 1965-1966 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Oastler Contacts, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Operations Analysis, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Plant Ecology, 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 30-31)
    - The Social Sciences - Statement of Need, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Tree Physiology, 1965-1970 (Box 38, Folder 33-40)
    - Wildlife Ecology, 1964-1965 (Box 39, Folder 41-42)
    - Wildlife Ecology, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - Wood Science, 1966-1968 (Box 39, Folder 44-45)
    - Wood Technology, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - Miscellaneous Inquiries, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 47)
- Records of Charles H. W. Foster, 1975-1981; Accession 1982-A-019
  The records in this accession are closed until January 1, 2016 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
  Campaign for Yale records are closed until January 1, 2053 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
  - Administrative Notes-Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alaska Lands Symposium-New Haven
    - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings in Transcript, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Meeting-Madison, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Association of Science-San Francisco Meeting, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Bar Association on Environment-Airlie House Conference, Virginia, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Foresters, Society of:
    - Washington, D.C., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Lufkin, Texas, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Orlando, Florida, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Council of Forestry School Executives, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Forestry Association/Yale Appalachian Trail Project, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - American Land Forum Meeting, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Appalachian Trail Matters, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Appalachian Trail Project Office, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 14-16)
  - Appalachian Trail Symposium
    - Proceedings, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 17-18)
    - Symposium Planning Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Belmont Colloquium: Elkridge, MD, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Biopolitics Symposium-New Haven, CT, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Brown University Lecture: "Balancing Community Interests: the Northfield Mountain Experience", 1979 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Campaign for Yale:
    - Alumni Breakfast, Denver, CO, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Atlanta Trip, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Chicago Horticultural Society-Dedication and Speech, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Coastal Zone Symposium, New Haven, CT, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Conservation Commissions and Speech to Federated Garden Clubs, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Conservation Foundation, Inc., The
    - 1976 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - 1981 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Board of Trustees, Columbia, MD, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Conservation Meeting: Vermont, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Continental Forest Industries: Visit of Walter Herbst and Ronald Mario, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Eisenmenger, Robert [See: Mergen, Folder 93], 1972-1977
  - Ellis Island, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Ford Foundation/Conservation Foundation, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Forest Club of Greenwich, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Forestry Deans' Tour of Alaska, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - General Seminars Program, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - History of the Yale Forestry School, Materials on, circa 1977 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Housatonic Valley Association "Environmental Event", 1980 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Human Dimensions in Wildlife Management, New Haven, CT, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - International Society of Arboriculture, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Long Island Sound Task Force-State of the Sound Conference, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Marine Fisheries Advisories Committee, San Diego Meeting, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Massachusetts, University of (Amherst)-Annual Awards Speech, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Meetings and Lectures Materials, Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Mellon, Andrew-Student Research Grant Program: New York, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Michigan, University of
    - Alumni Conference, New Orleans, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Presidential Inauguration, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Monongahela National Forest Trip, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 49-50)
  - National Conference on Citizen.Participation, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - New England Environmental Conference-Tufts University, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - New England Environmental Mediation Center-Boston, MA, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - New England Environmental Mediation Project Meeting, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - New England Natural Resources Center:
    - Mediation Conference, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Trustees Meeting, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - New England River Basins Commission, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - New Hampshire, University of-Meeting concerning Foundation of Forestry Information Center, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - New Haven Foundation: Proposal, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Newton Forest Association-Materials, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - North Idaho Ground and Air Tour, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 61-62)
  - Northeast Conference on Non-Industrial Private Forestry, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Northeastern Forest Insect Conference, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Northeastern Forestry Research Advisory Committee, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Promotional Materials, 1975-1980 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - "Recreation Program Needs: 1981 to the 21st century", 1979 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Regional Plan Association, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Research Proposal-"Removal of Atmospheric Particles by Leaves and Twigs of Urban Trees'', 1977 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - San Francisco Speech to Business Leaders-News Release, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - School Symposium: Dr. R. Patrick-River Ecosystems, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Seven Springs Forum, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Simsbury House, Sirnsbury, Connecticut, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Soil Conservation Society of America, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Student Conservation Association
    - Annual Meeting, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Board of Directors, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Suffolk University/Boston School of Management, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Technical Planning Associates-Brownstone-Boston, MA, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Texas A and M University-Visiting lecturer, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Vermont Law School-Environmental Conference, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Washington Trip, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Waterville Valley-New England/New York Private non-Industrial Forestry Seminar, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Westminster School, lecture, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Weyerhauser Company Foundation, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - White Memorial Foundation: Litchfield, CT, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Wingspread Conference on "Minority Education", 1978 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Wood Energy, Conference on, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Woods Hole
    - Annual Meeting, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Oceanographic Institution, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Yale Alumni Seminar, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Yale Council, Trip to St. Paul, MN, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Yale School of Forestry, Special Projects, 1975, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Campaign for Yale
    Campaign for Yale records are closed until January 1, 2053 due to University policies set by the Yale Corporation.
    - St. Paul-Minneapolis, MN, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - West Coast Trip, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Faculty Position, Quantitative and Systems Ecology, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 95-98)
    - Faculty Position, Quantitative and Systems Ecology, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 99-100)
- Records of Charles H. W. Foster, 1965-1980; Accession 1983-A-019
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2015
  - Alumni, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Day, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alumni-West Coast, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Academy for the Advancement of Science Meeting-Boston, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Appalachian Trail, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Black, Hallie-Forest School News, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bulletins-(Forestry School), 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Campaign for Yale, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Commencement, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
  - Connecticut Council on Water Company Lands, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
  - Consortium for Environmental Studies-"Particulate Metal Influence on Foliar Pathogens of Urban Trees", 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Deanship Search, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 17-18)
  - Dorr Nature Laboratory, Washington, CT, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - "Ecological Aspects of Natural Resource Management"-Fund Raising Committee for Proposal, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Facom Archives Committee, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Faculty, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Committees
    - Continuing Education, 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Curriculum Revision, 1970-1977 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Degree and Academic Standing, 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Distinguished Professional Service (Special), 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Junior Faculty, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Liaison with the Institution for Social and Policy Studies, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Sigma Xi Representative, 1968-1976 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Memoranda, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 30-31)
  - Field Trips-Inner City School Children, 1968-1977 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Fifth Forest, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Forestry in Southern New England, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Forestry Library, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 35-36)
  - Forestry Library, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 37-38)
  - Good offices, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Harvard-Yale, 1971-1976 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Industrial Forestry Seminar (42nd), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Institution for Social and Policy Studies, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - International Forestry Lectureships, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - International Programs, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Island Resources Foundation, Virgin Islands (Internships), 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - "Issues in the Environmental Crisis"-Symposium, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 47-48)
  - Issues in the Environmental Crisis:
    - Volume I, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Volume II, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Johnson Reprint Company, 1965-1972 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Junior Faculty Evaluation Program, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Jury Duty, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Kendall Foundation, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Land use / Environmental Internships, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Landowner Seminar Series, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - "Limits to Growth" Publication, 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Maine Appalachian Trail Club, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - McIntyre-Stennis Act and Amendment, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Meetings and Conferences, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 65-66)
  - Name Change, 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Natural Resources Case Studies, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - New Hampshire Alumni Meeting, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Other Schools, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Provost, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Questionnaires, 1972-1978 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Reception, Dean's, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Reception for Dean Foster, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 74)